Thomas Andersen

Frontend Web-Developer

+45 50927061

Portfolio

"In all situations Mr Andersen acted in an extraordinarily responsible, result oriented and conscientious manner. Even for the most difficult challenges, he found very effective solutions, which Mr Andersen always implemented successfully, achieving very good results. The quantity of work he completed and pace at which he worked fulfilled expectations." – Zalando SE

Skills

• HTML | CSS | JavaScript | ReactJS | Frontend | REST API (Basic understanding) | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | Git | GitHub | Music Production | Audio Engineering | English (C2) Danish (C2) German (B2)

Experience

Frontend Developer Trainee

Kreativstorm

Berlin, Germany - 08/09/2024 - 05/10/2024

- Collaborating with development teams to build responsive, accessible websites using semantic HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Learning and applying best practices in front-end development to create user-friendly interfaces.
- Participating in code reviews and improving code quality by following industry standards and modern practices.
- Utilizing Git for version control and collaborating on projects.

Customer Care Specialist

Zalando

Berlin, Germany - 01/04/2022 - 31/03/2024

- Specialist in the Customer Care International department of Europe's leading online platform for fashion Zalando. Being the forefront of a 6 billion EUR company dealing with customer inquiries via email, telephone and chat.
- Processing escalation cases with high priority and handling fraud prevention measures.
- Handling connected retail cases and working as support for stakeholders in B2B support.
- Utilizing both Salesforce as well as CR Tools to handle inquiries from the partners.

Music Producer/ Audio Engineer

Self-employed

Berlin, Germany - 01/07/2018 – Current

- Worked with multiple artists, producing, mixing and mastering music while planning / managing the releases.
- Produced more than 130 instrumental beats for artists to buy or lease through own website.
- Sold more than 200 instrumental beats for artists worldwide.
- Recoded, mixed & mastered close to 100 guitar loops for other beat makers and producers.
- Creating and testing clear and compelling copywriting for digital ads, landing pages and automated email-campaigns.

Education

Full-stack Web Development

Altcademy (Bootcamp)

Remote - 01/01/2024 - Current

Full-stack Web Development with Data Science & Applied AI

Bachelor of Arts (Hons)

BIMM University *Berlin, Germany -* 01/10/2015-01/07/2018

• Major in Songwriting (Graduating with a First Class Honours Degree).